Guide to the Frank Parsons Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- WRITINGS, 1890, 1894-1895, 1897-1908; Series IV; 3 linear feet (6 Boxes)
  - Outlines and Notes
    - Memory, notes, outlines on, undated (Box 8, Folder 343)
    - Municipal Government, notes, outlines on, undated (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Municipal Ownership, notes, outlines on, 1907-1908 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Political Economy, notes, outlines on, undated (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Psychology, notes outlines on, undated (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Public Ownership, notes, outlines on, undated (Box 9, Folder 348-349)
    - Railways, notes, outline on, undated (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Miscellaneous Outlines and Notes, 1899-1908 (Box 9, Folder 351)
    - Miscellaneous Notebooks, 1890, undated (Box 9, Folder 352)
    - Cottrell, Lucy M., notes on Psychology and Logic, undated (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - Noyes, Franny C., notes on 19th Century history (Book I), undated (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - Noyes, Franny G., notes on 19th Century history (Book II), undated (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Suggestions in relation to planning a government for the city of Boston, undated (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Brief on second class mail, undated (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Letters to the editors, undated (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Poems, 1894, undated (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Fragments of writings, 1898-1908 (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Other People's Writings
    - Denlinger, H: A Plan for Combining Primary and General Elections into Single. Election and to Provide for Proportional Representation in the City Council of Portland, Oregon, 1908 (Box 10, Folder 361)
  - Hirschler, Diana, "Store Suprintendency", Part II, undated (Box 10, Folder 362)
  - Littlefield, George E., "An Ascending Scale of Economic Attitudes", "The Gospel of Socialism", undated (Box 10, Folder 363)
  - Lloyd, William Bross, "Is a general act of legislature delegating general power to municipal corporations…Constitutional?", undated (Box 10, Folder 364)
  - Unknown author, "Paul Doherty", undated (Box 10, Folder 365)
  - University of Wisconsin, Extension Division: Business course 144, City and Town Promotion, undated (Box 10, Folder 366)
- MISCELLANEOUS, 1889-1908; Series V; 0.25; (1 box)
  Miscellaneous contains financial records, maps of New York City, Pacific City, newspaper clippings and printed materials.
  The arrangement is alphabetical by type of record and chronological within the folder.
  - Financial Records, check books, deposit record book, cancelled checks, 1906-1908 (Box 10, Folder 367)
  - Financial Records, invoices, and receipts, 1902-1908, undated (Box 10, Folder 368)
  - Maps, New York City and Pacific City, 1891, 1889 resp. (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1890-1908 (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Printed Materials, 1895 (Box 10, Folder 371)